<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Omaha Real Estate Podcast with Tracy Frans</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://localhost:4000"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from eXp Realty - your professional Omaha Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor>Tracy Frans</managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2019-09-23 14:45:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright>Tracy Frans</media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">Education</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>tracy@tracyfrans.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name>Tracy Frans</itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Tracy Frans</itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="http://localhost:4000/img/podcast.jpg"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Omaha Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from eXp Realty - your professional Omaha Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="Education"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dodgeball & Donate Day</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/dodgeball-donate-day.html</link>
        
        <author>Tracy Frans</author>
        <pubDate>2019-09-23 09:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Dodgeball+%26+Donate+Day.mp4</guid>
        <description>

I’m super blessed to be in the best industry ever—but now it’s time to give back. 

Join us on October 7 from 10 a.m. to noon for Dodgeball and Donate Day.HWA Warranty will be sponsoring a smoothie truck, and all donations go toward filling hope totes for the Open Door Mission. All you have to do is bring essential items like shampoo, conditioner, toothbrushes, and similar. 

Be sure to save the date! We look forward to seeing you there. 

As always, if you have any questions for us here at eXp Realty, don’t hesitate to reach out! 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Dodgeball+%26+Donate+Day.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Dodgeball+%26+Donate+Day.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>I’m super blessed to be in the best industry ever—but now it’s time to give back. Join us on October 7 from 10 a.m. to noon for Dodgeball and Donate Day. HWA Warranty will be sponsoring a smoothie truck, and all donations go toward filling hope totes for the Open Door Mission. All you have to do is bring essential items like shampoo, conditioner, toothbrushes, and similar. To see my full message, watch this short video.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Tracy Frans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>I’m super blessed to be in the best industry ever—but now it’s time to give back. Join us on October 7 from 10 a.m. to noon for Dodgeball and Donate Day. HWA Warranty will be sponsoring a smoothie truck, and all donations go toward filling hope totes for the Open Door Mission. All you have to do is bring essential items like shampoo, conditioner, toothbrushes, and similar. To see my full message, watch this short video.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Providing Our Clients a Better Experience Through Technology</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/providing-our-clients-a-better-experience-through-technology.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        <author>Tracy Frans</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-29 09:27:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Providing+Our+Clients+a+Better+Experience+Through+Technology.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I’m joined by Cody Levinson of Churchill Mortgage to talk about how we implement a couple of key pieces of technology into our business to give our clients—in this case, homebuyers— a better overall experience. 

First, an important way we speed up the home buying process and get to know our buyers is by getting them pre-approved, and now we’re able to text them an app that speeds up the pre-approval process and gives us more insight into the mortgage field. 

Churchill developed this co-branded app to not only streamline the pre-approval process, but also to make the loan process accessible anywhere, anytime. We use this for both our millennial and senior homebuyers, and it’s been able to put keys in homes quicker. 

A common question Realtors and the vendors they work with (especially loan officers) ask themselves is, “What do we do to buy leads? Do we spend money on Zillow and split that cost?” We’ve realized that once you start spending money on Zillow, though, you might never stop. 

“Partnering with a vendor who knows how to partner with technology not only increases our business, but it also provides a better experience to our clients.”

Well, we’ve been able to take our Zillow users and convert them to our own app called Homescout. Usually, about two weeks after using this app, they stop searching Zillow. It’s free, MLS-accessible, password-protected, and you can save and customize your home searches. It provides you with all sorts of data from various neighborhoods to help with your customization. 

This app isn’t branded through our brokerage or Churchill Mortgage, so if we were to move, you could still use it for the next two or three years. Nobody is selling their leads, and you won’t see other agents on it. I have instant back-end monitoring of all users. I can see who’s clicked on their homes, offer them seller property disclosures, and keep their buying process going without having to reach out to them. 

This insight has been tremendously beneficial, and it’s helped grow our business along with Churchill Mortgage. Partnering with a vendor who knows how to partner with technology not only increases our business, but it also provides a better experience to our clients. 

If you have any questions about these apps or our vendor partnerships, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d love to speak to you. 
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Providing+Our+Clients+a+Better+Experience+Through+Technology.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Providing+Our+Clients+a+Better+Experience+Through+Technology.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>We’ve implemented a couple key pieces of technology into our business to better serve our clients.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Tracy Frans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>We’ve implemented a couple key pieces of technology into our business to better serve our clients.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Do You Use Virtual Training in Your Business?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/do-you-use-virtual-training-in-your-business.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Tracy Frans</author>
        <pubDate>2019-08-08 10:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Do+You+Use+Virtual+Training+in+Your+Business_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

All agents agree that education is important, but what’s it doing for your business? How do you access that education?

Virtual training is a major reason for our success. As a tool, it provides plug-and-play, instantaneous education. Your education needs to be usable and attainable at any time, which is why we have weekly training sessions involving high-level real estate discussions that are recorded—so you can watch them whether it’s 9 a.m. or 9 p.m. 

Another important way to implement education into your business is the dashboard. We love our dashboard recording. It gives us a 90-day out and a 120-day out. You have to know what’s going on in your business to make agile decisions on the run—not just for marketing and team growth, but also to serve your clients in the best way possible. 

A big part of your education is also who you collaborate with. Is it someone local or national? We’ve enjoyed collaborating with agents who were at $5 million and looking to get to $8 million. Are you a team leader who’s at $10 million and wants to get to $20 million? Have you been in the industry for 40 years and are looking for your way out?

“You have to know what’s going on in your business to make agile decisions on the run.”

In any case, you need the type of education that suits your business. Don’t fall into the “one-education-fits-all” trap. Find people who will help you grow and do specifically what you’re looking to do in your business. 

Zoom calls have also been very effective in bringing agents together on a national scale, for mastermind groups, continuing education, and giving and getting value from other countries and states experiencing tremendous success. If you haven’t gotten into Zoom, just know that it’s the future of communication in our industry. I challenge you to connect with Zoom because it will change your day and make you more efficient every day. 

The power of virtual training is ready and waiting at your fingertips. The only question is, how high do you want to reach? 

If you have any questions about implementing virtual training into your education, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We’d love to show you all the tools we use and work with you to help serve all of our clients to the highest degree. We look forward to hearing from you. 

And remember—never stop learning!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Do+You+Use+Virtual+Training+in+Your+Business_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/Do+You+Use+Virtual+Training+in+Your+Business_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>As an educational tool, virtual training has greatly benefited our team, and it can do the same for you.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Tracy Frans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>As an educational tool, virtual training has greatly benefited our team, and it can do the same for you.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>What Advantages Does a Cloud-Based Brokerage Have?</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/what-advantages-does-a-cloud-based-brokerage-have.html</link>
        
          <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <author>Tracy Frans</author>
        <pubDate>2019-07-15 14:43:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/What+Advantages+Does+a+Cloud-Based+Brokerage+Have_.mp4</guid>
        <description>

There are basically only four business models that have ever existed in the real estate industry: local/traditional brokerages, national franchises, the boutique model, and cutting-edge cloud brokerage. A cloud-based brokerage represents a place where we can get together and work extremely efficiently along with our brokers, staff, and all agents with having the ability to work from anywhere. We’re paperless, but that’s one small part of being a cloud-based brokerage. We’ve increased our productivity while decreasing our operational costs. We’re able to get more help on our files more quickly than we ever could at a brokerage’s office. Most importantly, it’s allowed us to connect with top agents from around the world.
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/What+Advantages+Does+a+Cloud-Based+Brokerage+Have_.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Tracy+Frans/What+Advantages+Does+a+Cloud-Based+Brokerage+Have_.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>A cloud-based brokerage is efficient, mobile, and the future of real estate. Here’s why.</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Tracy Frans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>A cloud-based brokerage is efficient, mobile, and the future of real estate. Here’s why.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Welcome To Our Blog</title>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/welcome-to-our-blog.html</link>
        
          <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
          <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
          <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <author>Tracy Frans</author>
        <pubDate>2019-05-29 19:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid></guid>
        <description>Omaha is a great and thriving market right now, but as every agent agrees, things are changing quickly. 

We couldn’t be more excited about these changes and opportunities. 

So, we plan to upload two educational messages a month to give you insight into strategies and systems that will help your business thrive and how you, as an agent, can benefit from a business model that we have put into play. 

Check back because content will be coming soon!

We’re excited to keep you informed on how to promote your real estate career, and keep up with the constantly changing market!
</description>
        <enclosure url="" length="" type=""/>
        <media:thumbnail url="http://localhost:4000" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="" type=""/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Learn how our tips, tools, and insight into the market can help you advance your career in real estate!</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author>Tracy Frans</itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Learn how our tips, tools, and insight into the market can help you advance your career in real estate!</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in Omaha, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright>Tracy Frans</copyright>
    <media:credit role="author">Tracy Frans</media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from eXp Realty - your professional Omaha Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>
